Lionel Munje

Mississauga, ON Imunje414@gmail.com +1 647 219 5530

Hardworking Web Designer and a junior software developer successful at developing and updating Back-Front end interfaces to promote user engagement. Well-versed in custom designs, wireframe layouts and advanced web design principles. Highly experienced in HTML, CSS, ASP.NET and JavaScript. Successful developing mobile, desktop and phone applications that meet or exceed quality, usability and speed requirements.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Junior Software Developer

Pliteq Inc - Vaughan, ON February 2020 to Present

- Helped compose dedicated mobile and internet-only versions of software.
- Collaborated with It team to meet internal developer environment expectations.
- Assisted software planning, development and testing for server, client and web-based deployments.
- Built decoupled and service-oriented middleware software and platforms using visual studio code.
- Developed RESTful micro-services using Java.
- Contributed back-end development experience and collaborated on multiple APIs crucial to functionality.

Front End Web Developer

Pliteq Inc - Vaughan, ON February 2020 to Present

Web Designer

CSS Engineering - Douala, Littoral July 2019 to September 2019

- Presented solutions to complex design problems in presentations, click-through prototypes and design specifications.
- Developed site content and graphic by coordinating with copywriters and graphic artists.
- Interacted effectively with clients during design phase of projects to troubleshoot issues and gain valuable insight.
- Worked closely with product managers, visual designers and development team to appropriately evolve designs from concept to launch.
- Met with customers to determine and define goals surrounding graphics, design approaches and architecture.
- Oversaw facets of website projects throughout entire lifecycle.
- Mastered web designs from conception to completion and handled graphic design, artwork

and digital application.

Internship Student

Camsoft Group, Yaounde, Center July 2019 to September 2019

- Worked well in team environment as well as independently.
- Compiled, modeled and reported on data for staff members as directed.
- Worked with teams to support goals and build experience.
- Responded quickly to questions and inquiries via phone and email.

Education

College diploma in Computer Information Technology

Training TRIOS College - Mississauga, ON

October 2021 to Present

Bachelor Of Science in Information Technology

Saint Monica University

Skills

- · Web Security
- Front-End Programming: HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT (2 years)
- Interactive Prototypes
- · Design Software: Sketch, Invision,
- · Back-End and Database
- · Search Engine Optimization
- C++ Programming Language
- · Object-Oriented Programming
- Web and Application Servers
- Programming Languages: Java, C#, .Net (3 years)
- WordPress Design with Php (3 years)
- Database Management Software using firebase, MySQL (2 years)
- Design, Layout and Typography
- JS Frameworks: React, Angular, Vue (2 years)
- .NET Framework
- Adobe PhotoShop
- RDMS Development and SQL
- Eagerness to Learn New Technologies
- Javascript Libraries and Frameworks React , Angular (2 years)
- · Attestation of work from more than two work places
- Bootstrap
- · Microsoft SQL Server

- MySQL
- User Interface (UI)
- Node.js

Languages

- English Fluent
- French Intermediate